[{"answer": " Sorry. Thought I heard something", "docId": "pitch-black_shooting.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Like my pistola", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Tell me about the sounds. You told them you heard something right before....  If you don't talk to me, my friend'll take another crack at it", "docId": "pitch-black_shooting.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "What whispers", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " What, you don't really think they left with their clothes on the lines? Photos on the walls", "docId": "pitch-black_shooting.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I know you don't uncrate your emergency ship unless there's a fucking emergency", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " You're not a real cop, are you? Just some mercenary who goes around talkin' about the law like", "docId": "pitch-black_shooting.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Never said you were a hype, either", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "And here you got two mornings every day. Wow, were you  lucky", "docId": "pitch-black_shooting.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " made it a problem when you let my friend die like that. When you had enough drugs to knock out a fucking mul", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "There...", "docId": "pitch-black_shooting.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "It hurts them. Light actually hurts them...", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Look, we gotta think about everyone now", "docId": "pitch-black_shooting.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Smoke screen for what", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Think about that reward, my friend", "docId": "pitch-black_shooting.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "How 'bout a cut in your gut", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Let's move.  Just a detour. He'll get us there", "docId": "pitch-black_shooting.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "What, switch what", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Six of us left. If we could get through that canyon and lose just one, that'd be quite a fucking feat, huh? A good thing, right", "docId": "pitch-black_shooting.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "What if you're one of five", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Probably okay to talk to me now", "docId": "pitch-black_shooting.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Not sure. I was just runnin' away when this whole thing...", "qsentId": 22}]